box.co.uk 2019-12-14

# Privacy Policy - Box.co.uk

We at Box Ltd are totally committed to protecting your privacy. We comply with the principles of the UK Data Protection Act 1998 and the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003 subsequently incorporating the EU Cookie Regulations of May 2011. We conform with the EU General Data Protection Regulation from 25 May 2018.

## **Overview:**

Box Ltd trading as Box.co.uk. This privacy policy explains how we use any personal information we collect about you when you use our website www.box.co.uk and sign up to our marketing emails.

  * What information do we collect about you?
  * How will we use the information about you?
  * Email Marketing
  * Access to your information and correction
  * Cookies
  * Other websites
  * Changes to our privacy policy
  * How to contact us

## **What information do we collect about you?**

We collect information about you in order to process your order and send you our mailshots. That information will only be shared with other parties that are and deemed as a legitimate business interest. The information we hold may include:

  * Your Name
  * Postal / Delivery Address’s (required to deliver your order)
  * Password (encrypted record of your password)
  * Phone / Mobile Number (For delivery issues / Updates)
  * Email Address (Used as your login to our site)
  * Tokenised Card Details (Limited details to aid future purchases and refunds)
  * IP Address / Browser Type (Used for Payment / Fraud Checks)
  * Product Order / Invoice History (To fulfil any copy invoice’s / Warranty / Returns)
  * Email Marketing Data via “Tracking Pixels / Tracking Beacon” 
    * Recipient’s IP address, browser, email client type, Open time / Date and other similar Details.

## **How will we use the information about you?**

The collected information about you is used to process your order, manage your account and aid any further communication regarding your order. For example a request for warranty / support with your purchase in the future / Product Review / Feedback.

In the processing of your order, we may be required to share your details with our approved third parties:

  * Couriers – To provide required tracking and order updates for your order, Our most common courier partners are:
    * DPD
    * MyHermes
    * ArrowXL
    * Business Post
    * TNT

  * Finance / Payment Merchants – To complete the payment process for your order maybe:
    * PayPal
    * Amazon Pay
    * V12 Finance

  * Suppliers that offer certain ship direct product ranges:
    * Ingram Micro
    * Techdata
    * Exertis

  * Manufacturers only in the request of warranty work on your item we may be required to provide some Personal Data / Contact information. Ie if your product is within Warranty with a Manufacturer and we need to send the item off for repair on your behalf.

We will never collect sensitive information about you without your agreement. You have a right to ask for a copy of the information which we are holding and we will delete information or correct any inaccuracies for no charge as soon as you make the request.

We require all third parties to respect the security of your information and to treat it in accordance with the law. We do not allow our third-party service providers to use your information for their own purposes and only permit them to process your information data for specified purposes and in accordance with our instructions.

Data will only be released to other third parties (e.g. the police / HMRC) on request where there is a legal requirement for us to do so.

## **Email Marketing**

Box Limited use email marketing to reach out to our customers / subscribers to notify you all of our great deals. If you also agree to marketing communications, We share some of your personal information to approved third parties to offer a range of services / offers. This choice is offered to you during the signup process. At any time you can unsubscribe from this by clicking here  [www.box.co.uk/unsubscribe](http://www.box.co.uk/unsubscribe)

We use an award winning email client services from Mailchimp to send and create our email campaigns and below are the main key facts regarding their privacy policy which we feel are important to highlight and the full details are here: <https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/>

#### **_“Quoted as at 21/10/2019 from above url”_**

#### **_3A_**

##### **_A. Information We Collect_**

_The Personal Information that we may collect or receive about you broadly falls into the following categories:_  
_(i)   **Information we receive about Contacts from our Members** : A Member may provide Personal Information about you to us through the Services. For example, when a Member uploads their Distribution List or integrates the Services with another website or service (for example, when a Member chooses to connect their e-commerce account with Mailchimp), or when you sign up for a Member’s Distribution List on a Mailchimp signup form, they may provide us with certain contact information or other Personal Information about you such as your name, email address, address or telephone number. You may have the opportunity to update some of this information by electing to update or manage your preferences via an email you receive from a Member._  
_(ii)   **Information we collect automatically** : When you interact with an email campaign that you receive from a Member or browse or purchase from a Member’s connected store, we may collect information about your device and interaction with an email. We use cookies and other tracking technologies to collect some of this information. Our use of cookies and other tracking technologies is discussed more below, and in more detail in our Cookie Statement _[ _here_](https://mailchimp.com/legal/cookies/) _._

  * **_Device information_** _: We collect information about the device and applications you use to access emails sent through our Services, such as your IP address, your operating system, your browser ID, and other information about your system and connection._
  * **_Product usage data_** _: We collect usage data about you whenever you interact with emails sent through the Services, which may include dates and times you access emails and your browsing activities (such as what pages are viewed). We also collect information regarding the performance of the Services, including metrics related to the deliverability of emails and other electronic communications our Members send through the Services. This information allows us to improve the content and operation of the Services, and facilitate research and analysis of the Services._

_(iii)   **Information we collect from other sources** : From time to time, we may obtain information about you from third-party sources, such as social media platforms and third-party data providers. We take steps to ensure that such third parties are legally or contractually permitted to disclose such information to us, and we use this information to provide publicly available social media information about you to Members who have enabled the "Social Profiles" feature in their Mailchimp accounts. **”**_

## **Customer Service / Product Reviews**

Box Ltd pride ourselves on our customer service and keen to get feedback and reviews on our products / service that you receive from Box Ltd. We share your order details ie the product purchased and only your email address to request a review on our service / product to help us improve our products and services in the future.

Our Review Partner is Reevoo.com  
<https://www.reevoo.com/en/terms-conditions/>

## **Access to your information and correction**

You have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you. If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal information, please email or write to us at the following address. We want to make sure that your personal information is accurate and up to date. You may ask us to correct or remove information you think is inaccurate. Please email [data.protection@box.co.uk](mailto:data.protection@box.co.uk) with your request.

## **Cookies**

Cookies are text files placed on your computer to collect standard internet log information and visitor behaviour information. This information is used to track visitor use of the website and to compile statistical reports on website activity. For further information visit [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) or [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/). You can set your browser not to accept cookies and the above websites tell you how to remove cookies from your browser. However in a few cases some of our website features may not function as a result. If you would like advice and assistance here please contact at [data.protection@box.co.uk](mailto:data.protection@box.co.uk) and we will be happy to help.

## **Other websites**

Our website sometimes contains links to other websites. This privacy policy only applies to this website so when you link to other websites you should read their own privacy policies.

## **Changes to our privacy policy**

We keep our privacy policy under regular review and we will place any updates on this web page. This privacy policy was last updated on 22/10/2019.

## **How to contact us**

Please contact us if you have any questions about our privacy policy or information we hold about you:   
By Email – [data.protection@box.co.uk](mailto:data.protection@box.co.uk)  
By Phone – 0121 202 0000  
By Letter – FAO Data Protection Officer, Box Ltd, First Avenue, Minworth, Sutton Coldfield, B76 1BA  
In Person - Box Ltd, First Avenue, Minworth, Sutton Coldfield, B76 1BA
